steamid.eu 2017-03-17

# SteamID » Privacy Policy & Data

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which SteamID collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a "User") of the SteamID's website ("Site"). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by SteamID.

Regaurding STEAM and data from steam , Collecting and storing   
A user can request data about another user, This request is done via the STEAM COMMUNITY and data that is collect at the time will be available to the public.  
If you reach this page via a search engine, Any pages that search engines and other services choose to cache are out of SteamID's's control  
The data that SteamID's collects is publicly avalible , If you do not want your data stored we advise to change your steam community privacy settings.

What is the data we collect used for?   
The data that we collect about profiles is used to give the end user a better experience   
Such as: Displaying Friends list , Displaying Group Members , Showing people who are blocked from trading , Searching for names like %% and much much more

If you believe that we may be in breach of steams terms and conditions about the web API please read:  
http://steamcommunity.com/dev/apiterms 

Personal identification information

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways in connection with activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site.. We will collect personal profile information from the steam community website and via your account(s). Users can opt.  
to hide their profiles via steam. The profiles are publicly viewable and content that is hidden cannot be displayed. 

## Removal of profiles from this website

Profiles are pulled automatically from the steam community website.The Steam API third-party sites like SteamID to access this profile data held on their servers. If you would like the data collected from the steam service removed, Please make your account private and any further information that is not publicly obtainable will stop being updated. Any existing data may however still be displayed.   
Non-personal identification information

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

Web browser cookies

Our Site may use "cookies" to enhance User experience. User's web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

How we use collected information

SteamID may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:

\- To personalize user experience  
We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site.  
\- To improve our Site  
We may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services.

How we protect your information

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.

Sharing your personal information

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.

Third party websites

Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website's own terms and policies.

Advertising

Ads appearing on our site may be delivered to Users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile non personal identification information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

Google Adsense & Analytics

Some of the ads may be served by Google. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to Users based on their visit to our Site and other sites on the Internet. DART uses "non personally identifiable information" and does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, etc. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

Changes to this privacy policy

SteamID has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

Your acceptance of these terms

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy and terms of service. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

Contacting us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at:  
SteamID  
SteamID's

This document was last updated 17/07/2015
